levenger.com 2008-06-15

# Levenger Privacy Statement - Levenger

Levenger Privacy Statement

Last updated 10/1/07

AT LEVENGER, WE STRIVE TO TREAT OUR CUSTOMERS AS WE DO OUR BEST FRIENDS. SO IN DEVELOPING THIS PRIVACY POLICY, WE APPLIED THE GOLDEN RULE TEST: IF WE WERE THE CUSTOMER, HOW WOULD WE WANT THE COMPANY TO TREAT US? OUR GOAL IS TO RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY EVEN AS WE GO ABOUT THE BUSINESS OF BRINGING YOU WELL-DESIGNED AND USEFUL PRODUCTS FOR YOUR READING, WRITING AND THINKING. 

Information Collection and Use

Levenger is the sole owner of the information collected on www.levenger.com. Levenger collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

Registration:  
(Request a catalog/Join our e-list/E-contest/Create an Account and Add Your Review)  

If you request a catalog, join our e-list or sign up for our e-contest a user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address and email address). We use this information to send the customer a catalog and/or marketing emails. It is optional for the user to provide unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. We rent our customer’s mailing address with other third party catalog companies. If you wish to remove your name from third party rentals, it can be done by emailing our Customer Support at [cservice@levenger.com](https://www.levenger.com/customer/service/email/ContactEmailOrd.asp?Email=Cservice@levenger.com&Typ=2). Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. If you submit a comment for Add Your Review, we collect your name, email, and city/state to use as part of the testimonial for the product. We do not use your email address for marketing purposes but we may use it to contact you directly regarding your feedback. As stated on the Add Your Review page, by submitting your information and comments, you authorize us to print your name and comments as a review for the product listed. 

Order

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes, to fill customer’s orders and to send the customer a catalog. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is also used to contact the user. We rent our customer’s mailing address with other approved third party direct marketing companies. If you wish to remove your name from third party rentals, it can be done by emailing our Customer Support at [cservice@levenger.com](https://www.levenger.com/customer/service/email/ContactEmailOrd.asp?Email=Cservice@levenger.com&Typ=2). Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. We use persistent cookies with our service providers, Tealeaf, Coremetrics, and Dotomi. This allows us to track our customer’s visit on Levenger.com and help improve our web site’s functionality, navigation and performance. Once you close your browser, we do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer. 

We recognize that you have a choice to refuse cookies. If you choose not to accept the Levenger cookie, you may still use our site for browsing but purchasing is not possible. By choosing to accept the Levenger cookie, we will save items in your shopping bag for 5 days and you will not have to log in more than once during each visit (user must close browser to end visit), thereby saving time while on our site. 

If you are shopping Levenger and are having difficulty adding product to your shopping cart or completing your order, please check your privacy settings in your browser. Your privacy setting should be set at “Medium” to shop at Levenger. If you prefer not to change your privacy settings, you can always place your order by phone at 800-677-8034. 

Third Party Cookies

Levenger has engaged Coremetrics, a third party service provider, to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from visitors to the website to help us administer our web site in order to constantly improve the web site quality. We do track and analyze personally identifiable usage for customers who have completed a purchase, requested a catalog or signed up for our e-list. Coremetrics uses cookies to help track visitor behavior and Levenger sets cookies that will be listed under the domain lev.levenger.com. Coremetrics does not use cookies to relate website visitors to any personally identifiable information and provides Levenger with information about site usage that reflects individual behavior of visitors, but not their identity. All data collected by Coremetrics on behalf of Levenger is used only to provide us with information on site usage and is not shared with any other third parties. If you would like to deactivate our ability to analyze your anonymous browsing and purchase behavior through the use of this service or find out more about our service provider, including its privacy policy and how to opt out, go to: Opt-out 

Levenger has an advertising contract with Dotomi to serve display ads on our behalf across the Internet. Dotomi will collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may use information about your visits to this website to target advertisements for goods and services. These targeted advertisements may appear on our site or on other sites that you visit. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. If you do not want Dotomi to collect this information you may opt out. Opting out will not in any way, affect your use of our site. In order to opt out please click here. 

Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service. We use a tracking utility called Deepmetrix and Tealeaf that use log files to analyze user movement. 

Clear Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs). Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are are used throughout our site to track sales and statistical information from visitors to the web site. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of a period at the end of a sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable information.

In addition, we use clear gifts in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails or change the type of email they receive to text, please see the Opt-out section. 

Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates

Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections. 

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

Sharing

These are the instances in which we will share users’ personal information:

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

Personalized Cards Font Agreement

  1. You acknowledge that this server-based CUSTOMER Product contains, as a component, font software which generates font designs (“Font Software”).
  2. You agree that as used herein, the term “Internal Use” shall mean use of the CUSTOMER Product only in the course of your customary and ordinary internal business or personal use. “Customary and ordinary internal business use” shall mean use by you, your employees, or your authorized agents for your customary and ordinary internal business. “Customary and ordinary personal use” shall mean use by you or a member of your household for internal personal purposes. “Internal Use” shall occur when an individual permitted by this Paragraph 2 is able to give commands (whether by keyboard or otherwise) from a remote location that are followed by the Font Software which is a component of the CUSTOMER Product. Internal Use shall not include any use of the CUSTOMER Product (i) in the case of “customary and ordinary internal business use,” by persons that are neither your authorized employees nor authorized agents, or (ii) in the case of “customary and ordinary personal use,” by persons that are not members of your household. All such employees, agents, and household members shall be notified by you as to the terms and conditions of this End User Agreement and shall agree to be bound by it.
  3. CUSTOMER hereby grants you the non-exclusive, non-assignable, and non-transferable right to use this server-based CUSTOMER Product and its components only for your “Internal Use” and for no other purposes, including but not limited to, further resale, sublicensing, or distribution. All rights not expressly granted in this license are reserved by CUSTOMER.
  4. You may not alter Font Software which is a component of the CUSTOMER Product for the purpose of adding any functionality which such Font Software did not have when presented to you as part of the CUSTOMER Product. You may not extract the Font Software from the CUSTOMER Product or from CUSTOMER’S server. You may not copy the Font Software from the CUSTOMER Product or from CUSTOMER’S server.
  5. Internal Use shall not include any distribution whatsoever of the CUSTOMER Product or any component thereof, provided however, that you may electronically distribute a document created by you in the scope of Internal Use which contain Font Software in a static graphic image or in a format that permits the embedding of Font Software solely for the viewing and printing (and not the editing, altering, enhancing, or modifying) of such document. You may not embed Font Software into a document, which is distributed as a commercial product in exchange for a fee or other consideration (For example, End Users shall not embed Font Software into an electronic book that is offered to the public for a fee).
  6. This license does not transfer any right, title, or interest in the CUSTOMER Product or its components to you except as specifically and expressly set forth herein. You are on notice that CUSTOMER claims protection of this software product under copyright laws. Components of the CUSTOMER Product may have been developed by an independent third party software supplier, which holds copyright or other proprietary rights to its software product. You may be held responsible by this supplier for any infringement of such rights by you.
  7. CUSTOMER reserves the right to terminate this license upon breach. In the event of termination, you will be required to immediately cease all use of the CUSTOMER Product and Licensed Font software residing therein, destroy the original and all copies of the CUSTOMER Product in your custody, possession, or control and promptly certify to CUSTOMER that such destruction has taken place.
  8. If this product is acquired under the terms of a (i) GSA contract - use, reproduction or disclosure is subject to the restrictions set forth in the applicable ADP Schedule contract, (ii) DOD contract - use, duplication or disclosure by the Government is subject to restrictions set forth in subparagraph (c)(1)(ii) of 252.277-7013; (iii) Civilian agency contract - use, reproduction, or disclosure is subject to 52.277-19(a) through (d) and restrictions set forth in the accompanying End User Agreement. All rights reserved under the copyright laws of the United States.

Third Party Intermediaries

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, an outside telemarketing company to take orders and a credit card processing company to validate charges for goods. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Service Providers

We partner with other third parties such as Experian and DoubleClick to provide specific services. For example, DoubleClick is our email vendor that transmits all of our marketing emails and Experian is responsible for the data processing and postal sortation for each catalog mailing. When the user signs up for these particular services, we share names, email addresses and mailing address information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Business Transitions

In the event Levenger Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via email or direct mail prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe or remove in the subject line in the email or email us at [cservice@levenger.com](https://www.levenger.com/customer/service/email/ContactEmailOrd.asp?Email=Cservice@levenger.com&Typ=2). We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the ACCOUNT INFO PAGES or the user may contact us at 800-544-0880 or at 420 S. Congress Avenue, Delray Beach, FL 33445 to opt-out. 

Users of our site will not be notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. 

Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Levenger Company, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Contests

Our site requests information from users via the e-contests. Participation in this contest is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. 

Email-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Levenger will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Levenger does not store this information. We use the information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. To learn more about SSL, follow this [link](http://www.levenger.com/customer/service/security.asp). 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [cservice@levenger.com](https://www.levenger.com/customer/service/email/ContactEmailOrd.asp?Email=Cservice@levenger.com&Typ=2). 

Supplementation of Information

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information for third-party sources. 

ID (Address) Verification

We use a third-party software to verify a user’s mailing address. 

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the Account Info page or by emailing our Customer Support at [ cservice@levenger.com](https://www.levenger.com/customer/service/email/ContactEmailOrd.asp?Email=Cservice@levenger.com&Typ=2).Or, contact us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will not post a notice on our Web site or notify users of the change via email or direct mail. 

Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

Phone: 800-544-0880

Fax: 800-544-6910

Email:

Postal Address: 420 S. Congress Avenue, Delray Beach, FL 33445
